<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Guilt Free Life]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Guilt Free Life]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/guilt-free-life/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2016 03:58:05 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/guilt-free-life/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Sometime this summer I realized that I no longer stashed my travel bags with the unused travel-sized personal care products that hotels provided daily for guests. In my past years of traveling, I was sure to stow away the unused shampoo deep in my suitcase, so that the housekeeping staff would restock it the next day. That way, I could bring it home for use during another trip.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/guilt-free-life/sometime-this-summer-i-realized-that-i-no-longer-stashed-my/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">58ab4d75-ee53-47cf-81f6-ac16da9757a9</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2016 03:57:41 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>I wonder if I should be the one to write about this subject just now, but they say that you learn by teaching. So yesterday, I quit my very well-paying job to...well I'm not sure what I am going to do. Being a Scanner (a term penned by Barbara Sher in her wildly successful book Refuse to Choose!: Use All of Your Interests, Passions, and Hobbies to Create the Life and Career of Your Dreams) I have a Basecamp account filled with money making options that span from beekeeping to equine stem cell generation. Each of these options provides opportunity for income, growth and life experience for me, but which should I do first?</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/guilt-free-life/i-wonder-if-i-should-be-the-one-to-write-about-this-subject/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">bf3ca35c-1d29-439b-b215-a488124f8f62</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2016 03:51:15 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Your Peace Affects Others]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Yesterday, my Internet went out. For a blogger that can be detrimental, especially if we forget how to actually write with a pencil on paper. I had been given homework after having an animal communicator visit this week to help diagnose my draft horse's behavioral problems and I was eager to write about it. The communicator is helping us learn to interact with our horses in a more natural manner; letting them be horses, for example, rather than high-stepping prisoners that should never misbehave.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/guilt-free-life/how-your-peace-affects-others/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">533559fe-5c34-4608-b625-236807c62d99</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2016 03:46:28 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>